Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX. Additions
  - Kaurouma, Patricia, 1982 (Folder 60.64)
  - Mucci, J. F., 1982 (Folder 60.65)
  - Pin, E. Jean, 1982 (Folder 60.66)
  - Schlessman, Mark A., 1982-1983 (Folder 60.67)
  - Shanley, Mary Lyndon, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.68)
  - Suter, Robert B., 1982-1983 (Folder 60.69)
  - Mellon Committee — Guidelines, Correspondence, etc.: David Schalk, Chair, 1981-1982 (Folder 60.70)
  - Mellon Committee — Listing of Grants, 1981-1983 (Folder 60.71)
  - Mellon Guidelines — Extra Copies, 1981 (Folder 60.72)
  - Mellon Committee, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.73)
  - Mellon Guidelines, 1979-1982 (Folder 60.74)
  - Stephen Sadowsky — Signature, 1981 (Folder 60.75)
  - Mellon Committee, 1980-1981 (Folder 60.76)
  - Sadowsky, Stephen — Chrono File, 1980-1981 (Folder 60.77)
  - Mellon File, 1980 (Folder 60.78)
  - Mellon Budget, 1980-1981 (Folder 60.79)
  - Recipients of Mellon Funds by Departments, 1980 (Folder 60.80)
  - Mellon Projects (Folder 60.81)
  - Mellon Committee, 1980-1981 (Folder 60.82)
  - Mellon Committee, 1980 (Folder 60.83)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Folder 60.84)
  - Recommendations to VBS from Mellon Ad Hoc, 1980-1981 (Folder 60.85)
  - Mellon Reports on Awards Received, 1979-1980 (Folder 60.86)
  - Mellon Reports on Awards Received, 1980 (Folder 60.87)
  - Mellon Reports on Awards Received, 1979-1980 (Folder 60.88)
  - Mellon Committee Recommendations, 1982 (Folder 60.89)
  - Harold Benson, 1980 (Folder 61.1)
  - Campbell, Kathy — Physical Education, 1981-1982 (Folder 61.2)
  - Cartwright-Smith, Jeffrey — Psychology, 1980-1981 (Folder 61.3)
  - Chandler, Kenneth A., 1979-1980 (Folder 61.4)
  - Constantinople, Anne — Psychology, 1981 (Folder 61.5)
  - Computer Science Studies Program, 1981 (Folder 61.6)
  - Farganis, James — Multidisciplinary Program, 1980-1981 (Folder 61.7)
  - Morgan, Susan — English Department, 1981 (Folder 61.8)
  - Faculty Seminar on Literary Theory and Interpretation — Murray, 1981 (Folder 61.9)
  - McCleary, 1980 (Folder 61.10)
  - McHugh, Thomas F. — American Culture Program, 1981-1982 (Folder 61.11)
  - Moore, Deborah D. — Jewish Studies, 1981 (Folder 61.12)
  - Pearson, Donald M. — Music Department, 1981 (Folder 61.13)
  - Ringle, Martin, 1980-1981 (Folder 61.14)
  - Mellon Grant — Requisitions, 1980-1982 (Folder 61.15)
  - Appenzellar, Jean, 1979 (Folder 61.16)
  - Asprey, Winifred, 1979 (Folder 61.17)
  - Beeks, Graydon, Jr. — Music — Mellon, 1979 (Folder 61.18)
  - Brisman, Husan H. — English Department, 1981 (Folder 61.19)
  - Bulow, Loretta, 1980 (Folder 61.20)
  - Kathy Campbell, 1980-1981 (Folder 61.21)
  - Constantinople, Anne, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.22)
  - Elizabeth Daniels, 1980 (Folder 61.23)
  - Sidney Geist, 1980 (Folder 61.24)
  - Grennan, Eamon, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.25)
  - Harris, Ben, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.26)
  - Johnson, Kenneth A., 1979 (Folder 61.27)
  - Benjamin G. Kohl, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.28)
  - Maurice Lee, 1980 (Folder 61.29)
  - Nancy C. Rich, 1980 (Folder 61.30)
  - Ringle, Martin, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.31)
  - Schalk, David L., 1979-1980 (Folder 61.32)
  - Schlessman, Mark A. — Biology Department, 1981 (Folder 61.33)
  - Tucker, Edward, 1979 (Folder 61.34)
  - Wallace, Patricia, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.35)
  - Carol Christensen, 1980 (Folder 61.36)
  - Duke Cathy, 1979 (Folder 61.37)
  - Judith L. Goldstein, 1980 (Folder 61.38)
  - Mary Shanley, 1980 (Folder 61.39)
  - Donald Spicer, 1980 (Folder 61.40)
  - Murray, Michal — Humanities, 1981-1982 (Folder 61.41)
  - Recommendation to VBS from Mellon Ad Hoc, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.42)
  - Organizational Notes, 1979-1980 (Folder 61.43)
  - Bulletin Board Items, 1987-1988 (Folder 61.44)
  - Bulletin Board Items — Death Notices, 1987-1988 (Folder 61.45)
  - Bulletin Board Items — Death Notices, 1986-1987 (Folder 61.46)
  - Bulletin Board Items, 1986-1987 (Folder 61.47)
  - Norma G. Kelley — Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Folder 61.48)
  - Norma G. Kelley — Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Folder 61.49)
  - Robert E. Parks — Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Folder 61.50)
  - Robert E. Parks — Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Folder 61.51)
  - Colton Johnson, Dean, 1985-1989 (Folder 61.52)
  - Virginia B. Smith — Correspondence, 1984 (Folder 61.53)
  - Virginia B. Smith — Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Folder 61.54)
  - Hunter, Mary-Alice — Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.1)
  - Kelley, Norma — Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.2)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.3)
  - Sheridan, D. M. — Correspondence with Trustees, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.4)
  - Sheridan, D. M. — Personal, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.5)
  - Sheridan, D. M. — Notes and Messages, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.6)
  - Smith, V. B. — Bulletin Board – Death Notices Only, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.7)
  - Smith, V. B. — Bulletin Board Items, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.8)
  - Correspondence — VBS: “When I Came to Vassar…”, 1981 (Folder 62.9)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Folder 62.10)
  - Kelley, Norma G. — Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Folder 62.11)
  - Parks, Robert E. — Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Folder 62.12)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Death Notices, 1985-1986 (Folder 62.13)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Bulletin Board Items, 1985-1986 (Folder 62.14)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1986 (Folder 62.15)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Folder 62.16)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1985 (Folder 62.17)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Folder 62.18)
  - Kelley, Norma G. — Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Folder 62.19)
  - Parks, Robert — Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Folder 62.20)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Notes and Messages, 1984-1985 (Folder 62.21)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Personal, 1984-1985 (Folder 62.22)
  - Hunter, Mary-Alice — Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Folder 62.23)
  - Kelley, Norma G. — Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Folder 63.1)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Personal, 1983-1984 (Folder 63.2)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Bulletin Board – Death Notices Only, 1983-1984 (Folder 63.3)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Notes and Messages, 1983-1984 (Folder 63.4)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Folder 63.5)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Folder 63.6)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Bulletin Board Items, 1984-1985 (Folder 63.7)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Death Notices, 1984-1985 (Folder 63.8)
  - Rosen, Warren A., 1980 (Folder 63.9)
  - Ross, Ken, 1978-1980 (Folder 63.10)
  - Sears, John Franklin, 1979-1984 (Folder 63.11)
  - Singer, Breit, 1979-1982 (Folder 63.12)
  - Slade, Margot F., 1969-1981 (Folder 63.13)
  - Smith, Robert C., 1975-1981 (Folder 63.14)
  - Solum, John H., 1969-1979 (Folder 63.15)
  - Spicer, Donald Zane, 1970-1986 (Folder 63.16)
  - Stellato, Anthony, 1980-1981 (Folder 63.17)
  - Sullivan, H. Patrick, 1970-1980 (Folder 63.18)
  - Stoller, David, 1978-1980 (Folder 63.19)
  - Streit, Margaret M., 1973-1983 (Folder 63.20)
  - Thomas, Sheila Smith, 1978-1985 (Folder 63.21)
  - Timm, Ruth, 1979 (Folder 63.22)
  - Tokay, Elbert, 1967-1981 (Folder 63.23)
  - Trainor, Roberta W., 1975-1985 (Folder 63.24)
  - Tremelling, Michael J., 1974-1987 (Folder 63.25)
  - Tucker, Edward B., 1978-1985 (Folder 63.26)
  - Elizabeth Villard, 1988 (Folder 63.27)
  - Ellen Waggener, 1981-1986 (Folder 63.28)
  - Weedin, Everett K. (Jr.), 1967-1980 (Folder 63.29)
  - Weiss, Sabrina L., 1980-1981 (Folder 63.30)
  - Williamson Jr., George, 1970-1981 (Folder 63.31)
  - Wilson, Carol, 1980-1984 (Folder 63.32)
  - Commission on Higher Education Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Folder 63.33)
  - Governance — President’s Office (Folder 63.34)
  - College Planning Council Meeting, Jan 1986 (Folder 63.35)
  - College Planning — Replies, 1984; (1 folder) (Folder 63.36)
  - Interdepartmental Memos, 1984 (Folder 63.37)
  - Institutes Discussion — College Planning Council, May 1985 (Folder 63.38)
  - College Planning Council, 1985-1986 (Folder 63.39)
  - Alt, Patricia, 1984 (Folder 64.1)
  - Asprey, Winifred, 1978-1987 (Folder 64.2)
  - Balogh, Sara C., 1971-1979 (Folder 64.3)
  - Barber, Leila, 1980-1985 (Folder 64.4)
  - Beck, Lily Y., 1983 (Folder 64.5)
  - Berkowe, Christiance, 1958-1980 (Folder 64.6)
  - Beye, Charles Rowan, 1984 (Folder 64.7)
  - Boyd, Lola E., 1978-1982 (Folder 64.8)
  - Brockmeyer, Margot G., 1964-1981 (Folder 64.9)
  - Browar, Lisa, 1982-1983 (Folder 64.10)
  - Chow, Grace, 1984 (Folder 64.11)
  - Christie, John A., 1968-1984 (Folder 64.12)
  - Clark, Evalyn A., 1980 (Folder 64.13)
  - Curtis, Ellen Chinn (Mrs. John Curtis), 1976-1981 (Folder 64.14)
  - De Campo, Leila, 1966-1982 (Folder 64.15)
  - Di Paolo, Maria Grazia, 1977-1985 (Folder 64.16)
  - Evans, Alan B., 1980-1982 (Folder 64.17)
  - Fortna, Evelyn Carr Nelson, 1979-1980 (Folder 64.18)
  - Fluck, Betty Lippman, 1960-1984 (Folder 64.19)
  - Betty Fluck, 1984 (Folder 64.20)
  - Fricker, Stephanie, 1976-1982 (Folder 64.21)
  - Gittleman, Anne I., 1954-1986; (1 folder) (Folder 64.22)
  - Goudy, Frances L., 1965-1981 (Folder 64.23)
  - Groves Earl W., 1964-1980 (Folder 64.24)
  - Hagstrom, Ann H., 1980 (Folder 64.25)
  - Ben Harris, 1985-1986 (Folder 64.26)
  - Meeting with Ben Harris, Oct 1984 (Folder 64.27)
  - Harris, Benjamin F., 1978-1985 (Folder 64.28)
  - Helfenbein, Catherine A., 1975-1980 (Folder 64.29)
  - Jaeger, Rita C. Dr., 1975-1982 (Folder 64.30)
  - Jarsulic, Marc, 1979-1982 (Folder 64.31)
  - Kapschutschenko, Ludmila, 1983 (Folder 64.32)
  - Kaufman, Jerome, 1978-1980 (Folder 64.33)
  - Kaurouma, Patricia, 1977-1982 (Folder 64.34)
  - Kelley, David, 1983 (Folder 64.35)
  - Knapp, Janet, 1971-1985; (1 folder) (Folder 64.36)
  - Kutch, Claire, 1979 (Folder 64.37)
  - Lacher, Maury, 1977-1979 (Folder 64.38)
  - Lang, William W., 1979-1981 (Folder 64.39)
  - Lachterman, David, 1982-1985 (Folder 64.40)
  - Linner, Edward R., 1980 (Folder 64.41)
  - Lipton, Lynn, 1971-1979 (Folder 64.42)
  - Lukas, Karen J., 1976-1983 (Folder 64.43)
  - Joan Lukach, 1971-1983 (Folder 64.44)
  - Lumb, Ethel Sue, 1959-1981 (Folder 64.45)
  - Dean Mace, 1984-1985 (Folder 64.46)
  - Maul, Shirley A., 1973-1981 (Folder 64.47)
  - Mellenthin, George, 1979 (Folder 64.48)
  - Middleton, Robert, 1965-1980 (Folder 64.49)
  - Mills, Sally Diann, 1982 (Folder 64.50)
  - Murphy, Joan E., 1962-1981 (Folder 64.51)
  - McCann, William J., 1974-1980 (Folder 64.52)
  - McGlinchey, Thomas J., 1978-1979 (Folder 64.53)
  - McKenzie, Margaret, 1961-1980 (Folder 64.54)
  - McKinney, Audrey May, 1979-1981 (Folder 64.55)
  - Oktay, Elizabeth, 1966-1981 (Folder 64.56)
  - Parker, Lloyd R. (Jr.), 1978-1985 (Folder 64.57)
  - Paulus, David L., 1977-1981 (Folder 64.58)
  - Pearson, Donald M., 1958-1980 (Folder 64.59)
  - Pickens, Lucien Alton, 1966-1980 (Folder 64.60)
  - Pope, Randolph D., 1983-1985 (Folder 64.61)
  - Puglisi, Roberta A., 1979-1981 (Folder 64.62)
  - Quan, Linda, 1980 (Folder 64.63)
  - Regnier, Jerome, 1969-1982 (Folder 64.64)
  - Ritterskamp, James J. (Jr.), 1966-1981 (Folder 64.65)
  - Robbins, Mary Ann, 1979-1981 (Folder 64.66)
  - Roman, Gail Harrison, 1980-1986 (Folder 64.67)
  - Fred Rosen, 1986-1988 (Folder 64.68)
  - Fred Rosen, 1985-1986 (Folder 64.69)
  - Fred Rosen, 1984-1985 (Folder 64.70)
  - Social Policy and Capital Accumulation (Fred M. Rosen), May 1983 (Folder 64.71)
  - Sheridan, Dixie — Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Folder 64.72)
  - D. M. Sheridan — Notes and Messages, 1981-1982 (Folder 64.73)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Bulletin Board Items, 1983-1984 (Folder 64.74)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Bulletin Board Items, 1981-1982 (Folder 64.75)
  - D. M. Sheridan — Correspondence with the Trustees, 1981-1982 (Folder 64.76)
  - Bulletin Board Items — Death Notices Only, 1981-1982 (Folder 64.77)
  - Hunter, Mary Alice — Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Folder 64.78)
  - Mary-Alice Hunter — Chrono., 1980-1981 (Folder 64.79)
  - Kelly, Norma — Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Folder 65.1)
  - Loesier, Marjorie — Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Folder 65.2)
  - Robbins, Mary Ann — Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.3)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Folder 65.4)
  - Norma Kelley — Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.5)
  - Bulletin Board Items — Death Notices Only, 1977-1981 (Folder 65.6)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.7)
  - Notes and Messages — D. M. Sheridan, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.8)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Folder 65.9)
  - Sheridan, Dixie M. — Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.10)
  - Sheridan — Correspondence with Trustees, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.11)
  - Dixie M. Sheridan — Personal, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.12)
  - Mackenzie, Marla — Assistant to the President: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Folder 65.13)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Bulletin Board Items, 1980-1981 (Folder 65.14)
  - Smith, Virginia B. — Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Folder 65.15)
  - Mackenzie, Marla — Assistant to the President: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Folder 65.16)
  - Robbins, Mary Ann — Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Folder 65.17)
  - Robbins, Mary Ann — Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Folder 65.18)
  - President’s Entertainment, 1984-1985 (Folder 66.1)
  - President’s Receptions, 1983-1984 (Folder 66.2)
  - President’s — Questions and Answers with Students and Administration, 1982-1983 (Folder 66.3)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1981-1982 (Folder 66.4)
  - President’s — Portrait at Bachrach, Sep 1981 (Folder 66.5)
  - President’s Dinner Honoring Gospel Choir, Feb 1984 (Folder 66.6)
  - Invitations to the President, 1985-1986 (Folder 66.7)
  - Poker Game — President’s House, May 1983 (Folder 66.8)
  - “Leaves Dinner”, Oct 1983 (Folder 66.9)
  - President’s Entertainment — Children’s Party, Jun 1980 (Folder 66.10)
  - Reception for Kenneth Chandler — President’s House, May 1986 (Folder 66.11)
  - President’s Picnic for HSE Fellows and HSE Presidents, Sep 1983 (Folder 66.12)
  - Poker Game — VBS, 1985 (Folder 66.13)
  - President’s Receptions — Fall, 1984 (Folder 66.14)
  - President’s Receptions, 1980-1983 (Folder 66.15)
  - President’s Reception During Reunion Weekend, Jun 1983 (Folder 66.16)
  - President’s Reception for Eleanor Clark and Robert Warren, Oct 1982 (Folder 66.17)
  - Reception for Black Admission and Financial Aid People, Sep 1983 (Folder 66.18)
  - President’s Reception in Honor of New Faculty, Sep 1983 (Folder 66.19)
  - Party for Retiring Faculty, May 1985 (Folder 66.20)
  - President’s Reception for Retiring Faculty, May 1983 (Folder 66.21)
  - President’s Entertainment — Pope Dinner, Apr 1984 (Folder 66.22)
  - Tea for Alumnae/I Working at Vassar, Feb 1985 (Folder 66.23)
  - President’s Invitation Prior to Curtis Lecture, Mar 1981 (Folder 66.24)
  - Invitations to the President, 1985-1986 (Folder 66.25)
  - Invitations to the President, 1984-1985 (Folder 66.26)
  - Invitations to the President, 1983-1984 (Folder 66.27)
  - Invitations to the President, 1982-1983 (Folder 66.28)
  - Invitations to the President, 1981-1982 (Folder 66.29)
  - Invitations to the President, 1981 (Folder 66.30)
  - Speeches (VBS), 1978-1981 (Folder 66.31)
  - Speeches (VBS), 1981-1982 (Folder 66.32)
  - Speeches (VBS), 1982-1983 (Folder 66.33)
  - Speeches (VBS), 1983-1984 (Folder 66.34)
  - Speeches (VBS) (After “Vassar Quarterly” Last Page), 1980-1981 (Folder 66.35)
  - Convocation Speech (VBS) — Gettysburg College, Sep 1983 (Folder 67.1)
  - Future Enrollments Speech Materials (Folder 67.2)
  - Creativity and Order — University of Delaware, Sep 1983 (Folder 67.3)
  - Speeches — University of Delaware, Sep 1983 (Folder 67.4)
  - President’s Reports and Statements, 1982-1983 (Folder 67.5)
  - FIPSE Speech, Jun 1981 (Folder 67.6)
  - Speeches — “Leaders”, 1982 (Folder 67.7)
  - Speeches (VBS) — Plagarism, 1978 (Folder 67.8)
  - Speeches (VBS) — “Views of Liberal Education: From the Periphery to the Center”, Jun 1981 (Folder 67.9)
  - VBS Speech — 1984 Symposium (Folder 67.10)
  - Speech Material (VBS), 1983-1984 (Folder 67.11)
  - Speech Material (VBS), 1980` (Folder 67.12)
  - Speeches (VBS) (Up to “Vassar Quarterly ‘Last Page’”), 1980-1981 (Folder 67.13)
  - Speeches (VBS) — Chemistry Building, Oct 1982 (Folder 67.14)
  - Bloomfield College — President Smith Commencement Address, Jun 1985 (Folder 67.15)
  - Bloomfield College Commencement, Jun 1985 (Folder 67.16)
  - President’s Trips — Alverno College, 1982 (Folder 67.17)
  - Alfred University Convocation, Sep 1985 (Folder 67.18)
  - La Grange Rotary Club — VBS Speaks, Apr 1985 (Folder 67.19)
  - Baltimore Opera Ball, Dec 1983 (Folder 67.20)
  - Empire State Conference, 1986 (Folder 67.21)
  - University of Delaware — Convocation: VBS to Speak – 150th Anniversary, Sep 1983 (Folder 67.22)
  - University of Delaware — Fall Convocation: VBS to Speak, Sep 1983 (Folder 67.23)
  - President’s Trips — De Paul University, 1982 (Folder 67.24)
  - James Madison University, 1985 (Folder 67.25)
  - Sounding Symposium, Nov 1985 (Folder 67.26)
  - NASA Teacher in Space Project, 1985 (Folder 67.27)
  - Presidential Seminar — Hunter College, Feb 1986 (Folder 67.28)
  - Advisory Commission on College and University Nonprofessional Legal Studies, Mar 1, 1986 (Folder 67.29)
  - Staff/Union Negotiations, 1986 (Folder 67.30)
  - Minutes from Negotiating Sessions, 1986 (Folder 67.31)
  - CWA Contract Proposals, 1986 (Folder 67.32)
  - Social Security Coalition, 1985 (Folder 67.33)
  - Staff Unionizing, 1983-1986 (Folder 67.34)
  - South Africa — Divestment Letters, 1986-1987 (Folder 67.35)
  - Brooklyn College Exchange, 1985 (Folder 67.36)
  - Burroughs Letters, 1985 (Folder 67.37)
  - [Student] (Extremely Confidential), 1987-1988 (Folder 67.38)
  - Mudd Chemistry, 1986 (Folder 67.39)
  - Department of Halls, 1985-1986 (Folder 67.40)
  - Mary Carroll Smith (Confidential), 1988 (Folder 67.41)
  - The Glenmede Trust Company, 1985-1986 (Folder 67.42)
  - Dorm Damage, 1985-1987 (Folder 67.43)
  - D.I.P. Yali-Manisi, 1987-1988 (Folder 67.44)
  - Green Haven Program, 1987 (Folder 67.45)
  - Minority Student Recruiting, 1985-1988 (Folder 67.46)
  - [Student] Appeal (Confidential), 1987 (Folder 68.1)
  - 1986 Undergraduate Summer Research Institute (Folder 68.2)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 1981-1984 (Folder 68.3)
  - cIcu and nyscIcu Boards of Trustees Meetings, Mar 1988 (Folder 68.4)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1980-1987 (Folder 68.5)
  - President’s Trip to (ACUNY) Rensselaerville, 1982 (Folder 68.6)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1978-1985 (Folder 68.7)
  - cIcu and nyscIcu Boards of Trustees Meetings, Jun 1988 (Folder 68.8)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1983-1987 (Folder 68.9)
  - cIcu and nyscIcu Executive Committees and Boards of Trustees Meetings, Jan 1989 (Folder 68.10)
  - cIcu/nyscIcu Annual Meeting, Mar 1987 (Folder 68.11)
  - cIcu/nyscIcu Annual Meeting, Mar 1987 (Folder 68.12)
  - nyscIcu Memorandum, 1987 (Folder 68.13)
  - Mellon Committee Budget, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.14)
  - Martin Ringle/et al., 1985 (Folder 68.15)
  - Gunter Klabes/Gail Roman, 1985 (Folder 68.16)
  - Marguerite Le Clezio, 1985 (Folder 68.17)
  - Mellon Applicants, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.18)
  - Thaddeus Gesek, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.19)
  - Lorrie Goldensohn, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.20)
  - David Guichard, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.21)
  - Andrew Jennings, 1985 (Folder 68.22)
  - Gunter Klabes/Gail Roman, 1984 (Folder 68.23)
  - Miriam Rossi, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.24)
  - Edward Tucker, 1984-1985; (1 folder) (Folder 68.25)
  - Mellon Committee Meeting — Recommendations, 1984 (Folder 68.26)
  - Mellon — Recommendations to the President, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.27)
  - Mellon Committee Correspondence File, 1984 (Folder 68.28)
  - Anne I. Gittleman, 1985-1986 (Folder 68.29)
  - Noel Jay Bean, 1985 (Folder 68.30)
  - Patricia Fabozzi, 1985 (Folder 68.31)
  - William Gifford, 1985 (Folder 68.32)
  - Randolph Cornelius (Sloan), 1985 (Folder 68.33)
  - John Feroe/Martin Ringle (Sloan), 1985 (Folder 68.34)
  - William Lunt/Robert Fritz (Sloan), 1985 (Folder 68.35)
  - Sondra Silverman (Sloan), 1984-1985 (Folder 68.36)
  - David Cox/William Straus (Sloan), 1984 (Folder 68.37)
  - Lawrence Herbst (Sloan), 1985 (Folder 68.38)
  - Lawrence Herbst, 1984 (Folder 68.39)
  - Glen Johnson, 1985 (Folder 68.40)
  - Stephen Rousseas, 1985 (Folder 68.41)
  - Robert Suter, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.42)
  - Mark Schlessman, 1985-1986 (Folder 68.43)
  - Guidelines, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.44)
  - Harry Roseman, 1985-1986 (Folder 68.45)
  - Mellon/Sloan List of Grants, 1985 (Folder 68.46)
  - Mellon — Confidential, 1986 (Folder 68.47)
  - Previous Mellon Reports, 1984-1985 (Folder 68.48)
  - Miscellaneous Loose Files, 1978-1987 (Folder 68.49)
  - Coeducation (VBS Letter and Report), 1983-1987 (Folder 68.50)
  - Eleanor Clark Papers, 1985-1987 (Folder 68.51)
  - Center for Integrative Studies, 1984-1988 (Folder 68.52)
  - Art Facilities, 1986-1988 (Folder 68.53)
  - Alcohol Law, 1985 (Folder 68.54)
  - Alumnae House, 1982-1986 (Folder 68.55)
  - Art Facility — Expanded Art Gallery and Building, 1979-1983 (Folder 68.56)
  - EZE/Adloff, 1984-1986 (Folder 68.57)
  - “Brissac” — Confidential, 1983-1984 (Folder 69.1)
  - Admissions Questionnaires, 1983-1984 (Folder 69.2)
  - Office of the Chaplain, 1983-1986 (Folder 69.3)
  - Chaplain, 1984-1986 (Folder 69.4)
  - CIRC, 1985-1986 (Folder 69.5)
  - College Planning Council — Correspondence, 1984 (Folder 69.6)
  - College Planning Council — Proposals, 1984-1985 (Folder 69.7)
  - College Planning Council Faculty Development, 1984 (Folder 69.8)
  - College Planning Council (memo to FPPC), Apr 1985 (Folder 69.9)
  - College Planning Council (FPPC Correspondence), 1985 (Folder 69.10)
  - College Planning Council (notes and extra copy), 1985 (Folder 69.11)
  - Computer Center Planning Proposals, 1984-1985 (Folder 69.12)
  - FPCC, 1985-1986 (Folder 69.13)
  - Comparable Worth, 1985 (Folder 69.14)
  - Administrative Computer, 1983-1984 (Folder 69.15)
  - Council on the Liberal Arts, 1985 (Folder 69.16)
  - Betty Daniels, 1984 (Folder 69.17)
  - Development Applicant Grants and Contracts, 1985 (Folder 69.18)
  - Dickinson-Kayden Fund (Events), 1984-1987 (Folder 69.19)
  - Eight Year Report, 1985 (Folder 69.20)
  - Early Retirement Plans, 1983-1984 (Folder 69.21)
  - Early Retirement Meeting, Dec 1985 (Folder 69.22)
  - Early Retirement Plans, 1983-1985 (Folder 69.23)
  - Communication on Extra-Curricular Events (Folder 69.24)
  - Facilities Financial Exposures, 1985 (Folder 69.25)
  - FASC, 1985-1986 (Folder 69.26)
  - New Faculty Equity (Folder 69.27)
  - Faculty Equity Issues, 1984 (Folder 69.28)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1985 (Folder 69.29)
  - Faculty Quality, 1983-1984 (Folder 69.30)
  - Faculty Research and Scholarship — Steinhorn and Church, 1984 (Folder 69.31)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1985 (Folder 69.32)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1983-1985 (Folder 69.33)
  - Freshman Norms, 1986 (Folder 69.34)
  - Gifts to Vassar, 1984-1985 (Folder 69.35)
  - Global Perspectives, 1985 (Folder 69.36)
  - Governance — Hiring Procedures (Prepared for VBS), Aug 1981 (Folder 69.37)
  - Harassment, 1985 (Folder 69.38)
  - Hewlett-Mellon, 1983-1987 (Folder 69.39)
  - Hewlett-Melon Program, 1983-1984 (Folder 69.40)
  - Higher Education Data System (HEDS), 1985 (Folder 69.41)
  - Mary Alice Hunter — Confidential, 1983 (Folder 69.42)
  - W. K. Kellogg Foundation, 1986 (Folder 69.43)
  - Lilly Endowment Program, 1984-1986 (Folder 69.44)
  - Levy, Jay, 1985 (Folder 69.45)
  - Lilly Endowment, 1984 (Folder 69.46)
  - Board of Regents, 1980, 1984 (Folder 70.1)
  - NYS Education Department — Regents Statewide Plan (Post-secondary Education), 1981 (Folder 70.2)
  - New York State Education Department — General, 1980-1981 (Folder 70.3)
  - New York State Concerns, 1982 (Folder 70.4)